You know
I want it I like
uh, just a glance and I'm swept away
uh 한순간 밀려온 눈빛
Wanna take a look inside you
Can't keep count
수없이
How many times I fall to my knees
허물어져도 좋을 맘은
This silly heart tumbles again and again
네게 기울어 기울어 또
Why why why yeah
Stay up
Making memories all night long
긴 밤 내내 쌓아 올린 기억
Maybe you were just bored
아마 그건 네게 의미 없는 장난이었는지
You smile and break toys for fun like a kid
아이처럼 날 무너뜨리곤 웃지
I'm broken
부서져 난
There's no warmth in your arms
온기 하나 없는 네 품에서
Your head on my shoulder, hinting forever
꼭 머무를 듯 기대와 넌
This time I won't fall for it
더 속지 않으려 해도
Poison that soaks my hardened heart
굳게 다진 맘을 적신 Poison
Poison, that's you breaking my breath
참은 숨을 파고든 넌 Poison
Those footsteps like clear, flowing water
투명한 그 발걸음이
That slowly swirls
천천히 휩쓸다
And at last tears me down
끝끝내 무너뜨려 나를
Poison in my mind
Dreaming bout you
Almost a warm embrace
감싸 안아줄 듯
Destruction in my mind
부숴 in my mind
Dreaming bout you
But now I’m Dreaming bout you
The higher the hope
커진 마음만큼
The harder I fall
무너져 난
Rehashing these feelings
이 감정들을 되짚곤
Swallowing the pain
삼켜 깊이
As you tear me apart
또다시 나를 헤집곤
Then run away, but still I
달아나도 난